<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>equality on Leftpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/equality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in equality on Leftpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/equality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>True equality is impossible</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/true-equality-is-impossible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/true-equality-is-impossible/</guid>
      <description>Equality is not &amp;ldquo;sameness.&amp;rdquo;
Equality acknowledges differences between people, but does not support distinctions such as race and gender as a basis for subjection.
Acknowledging differences is at the core of the concept of equality. In order for us to treat each other as equals, it is necessary that we first acknowledge and value our differences.
Treating people as equals is different than treating them the same. For instance, in education, giving students the same amounts of instruction, lessons, and identical learning materials is different than providing students with the necessary resources to reach educational goals and achieve academic success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re all just asking for special treatment, not equality!</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/youre-all-just-asking-for-special-treatment-not-equality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/youre-all-just-asking-for-special-treatment-not-equality/</guid>
      <description>Hmmm&amp;hellip; interesting.
In our view, straight (cishet) white men have been getting special treatment, instead of being equals to the rest of society.
Virtually any other demographic that is not white, cisgender, or male, has been on a disproportionate struggle of their own, no? It would be hard to argue that this has not been the case.
So what does that make our demands exactly? Furthermore, maybe you&amp;rsquo;re not exactly informed on what our demands are as Black American Socialists.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>