<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liberalism on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/liberalism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Liberalism on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/liberalism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I totally agree on race issues, because it&#39;s always divided us, which is why I think the economic stuff is just gonna divide us more. We need to unify behind achievable goals to end racism like leveraging corporate partnerships to encourage diverse hiring!</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-totally-agree-on-race-issues-because-its-always-divided-us-which-is-why-i-think-the-economic-stuff-is-just-gonna-divide-us-more-we-need-to-unify-behind-achievable-goals-to-end-racism-like-leveraging-corporate-partnerships-to-encourage-diverse-hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-totally-agree-on-race-issues-because-its-always-divided-us-which-is-why-i-think-the-economic-stuff-is-just-gonna-divide-us-more-we-need-to-unify-behind-achievable-goals-to-end-racism-like-leveraging-corporate-partnerships-to-encourage-diverse-hiring/</guid>
      <description>You are one step away from understanding the underlying cause of oppression, Capitalism.
The underlying assumption of a race-only solution is that when racial groups are forced together (through law and regulation), they will work out their differences, i.e. the &amp;ldquo;melting pot.&amp;rdquo; The antebellum South in the U.S. or apartheid South Africa are examples of intense, daily contact and deep familiarity between dominant and dominated individuals, where contact didn&amp;rsquo;t diminish prejudice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity politics have ruined the Left.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/identity-politics-have-ruined-the-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/identity-politics-have-ruined-the-left/</guid>
      <description>What do you mean when you say &amp;ldquo;identity politics&amp;rdquo; exactly?
Are you referring to race reductionism (people who reduce everything to race)?
Are you referring to people with different backgrounds moving in self-determination?
We think it&amp;rsquo;s important that we differentiate between Liberal identity politics, and Leftist identity politics. The former is a tool used by (Neo)Liberals to keep poor and working-class people divided, while the latter is about ensuring less-represented voices and concerns get heard in an international movement to dismantle Capitalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity politics make everything about race. This is really about class.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/identity-politics-make-everything-about-race-this-is-really-about-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/identity-politics-make-everything-about-race-this-is-really-about-class/</guid>
      <description>Identity politics is not synonymous with race reductionism (reducing everything to race).
We think it&amp;rsquo;s important that we differentiate between Liberal identity politics, and Leftist identity politics. The former is a tool used by (Neo)Liberals to keep poor and working-class people divided, while the latter is about ensuring less-represented voices and concerns get heard in an international movement to dismantle Capitalism.
If anything, class reductionism has &amp;ldquo;ruined&amp;rdquo; the (actual) Left while Liberals (not Leftists) with no conception of an anti-racist and anti-capitalist future have co-opted inherently anticapitalist concepts rooted in identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now is not the time to focus on identity politics! It drives us apart when we need to be united against Trump.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/now-is-not-the-time-to-focus-on-identity-politics-it-drives-us-apart-when-we-need-to-be-united-against-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/now-is-not-the-time-to-focus-on-identity-politics-it-drives-us-apart-when-we-need-to-be-united-against-trump/</guid>
      <description>Ignoring the struggles of marginalized people is exactly what Trump and fascists would want you to do, no?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics is all about compromise; we need to be able to meet the other side halfway.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/politics-is-all-about-compromise-we-need-to-be-able-to-meet-the-other-side-halfway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/politics-is-all-about-compromise-we-need-to-be-able-to-meet-the-other-side-halfway/</guid>
      <description>Most people agree that compromise is essential in electoral politics and &amp;ldquo;politics&amp;rdquo; in general. The failure of politicians to compromise is often attributed to political polarization of our country – that is, for the Right and the Left to come to the middle. However, Gutmann and Thompson argue that there is an internal tension in political compromise in that the democratic process requires politicians both to resist compromise and to embrace it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White people have done good and bad things; focus on the good.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/white-people-have-done-good-and-bad-things-focus-on-the-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/white-people-have-done-good-and-bad-things-focus-on-the-good/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; (all across the board and for all peoples) has long-term institutional consequences that need to be addressed; only focusing on the &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; won&amp;rsquo;t help those issues get solved.
Critical thinking and analyses matter, and we&amp;rsquo;re particularly focused on critical analysis that is constructive; we are seeking and acting upon solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>