<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cops on Leftpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/cops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cops on Leftpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/cops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cops have a hard job, and how do they know if some person is unarmed? If someone didn&#39;t follow directions, I&#39;d probably shoot them too. You have to listen to cops.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/cops-have-a-hard-job-and-how-do-they-know-if-some-person-is-unarmed-if-someone-didnt-follow-directions-id-probably-shoot-them-too-you-have-to-listen-to-cops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/cops-have-a-hard-job-and-how-do-they-know-if-some-person-is-unarmed-if-someone-didnt-follow-directions-id-probably-shoot-them-too-you-have-to-listen-to-cops/</guid>
      <description>Policing institutions have their roots in slave patrols, so just keep that in mind when you tell Black people that they &amp;ldquo;have to listen to cops.&amp;rdquo;
Cops may have a difficult job, but what seems more relevant is how dangerous it is (or isn&amp;rsquo;t).
Policing is not actually as dangerous in terms of fatalities per worker as numerous other jobs, including construction, logging, fishing, and agriculture. A lot of the cop fatalities we hear about are just car accidents and have nothing to do with intentional harm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On police brutality: &#34;These are just isolated incidents. Why don&#39;t they report on good cops?&#34;</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/on-police-brutality-these-are-just-isolated-incidents-why-dont-they-report-on-good-cops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/on-police-brutality-these-are-just-isolated-incidents-why-dont-they-report-on-good-cops/</guid>
      <description>Cops already have overwhelmingly positive media coverage.
For example, news outlets typically says things like &amp;ldquo;suspect was killed in a police-involved shooting&amp;rdquo; rather than &amp;ldquo;police shot an unarmed and compliant civilian.&amp;rdquo;
It&amp;rsquo;s actually a vanishingly rare circumstance where the news gives police brutality fair coverage; the reason it stands out in your mind is because it&amp;rsquo;s such an unusual happening.
If the news reported on police brutality (and the corruption that follows in allowing such officers to go free without meaningful consequence) in an unbiased manner, it would take wall-to-wall coverage every day of the year to address the scope of this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why don&#39;t Black people just not commit crimes and be polite and follow orders when dealing with cops? Always seems to work for me.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-dont-black-people-just-not-commit-crimes-and-be-polite-and-follow-orders-when-dealing-with-cops-always-seems-to-work-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-dont-black-people-just-not-commit-crimes-and-be-polite-and-follow-orders-when-dealing-with-cops-always-seems-to-work-for-me/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you not having to deal with trouble from cops has less to do with being &amp;ldquo;polite&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;following orders,&amp;rdquo; and more to do with not being Black. Either way, your rationale is purely anecdotal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>