<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>racist on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/racist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in racist on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/racist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Black people can be racist too; it&#39;s not just white people.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/black-people-can-be-racist-too-its-not-just-white-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/black-people-can-be-racist-too-its-not-just-white-people/</guid>
      <description>This all depends on what you mean when you say &amp;ldquo;racist.&amp;rdquo; Usually when someone says this, what they&amp;rsquo;re really trying to do is equate prejudices expressed or acted upon by Black Americans with the racism and prejudice of &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; Americans. This leaves out centuries of historical context, as well as the context of our present circumstances. Black Americans only make up 12.6% of the U.S. population and &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; Americans hold most of the institutional power, so it&amp;rsquo;s worth thinking about the big picture here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t see color. By seeing racism in all things, you&#39;re perpetuating it. If race is a construct why should we even acknowledge racism?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-see-color-by-seeing-racism-in-all-things-youre-perpetuating-it-if-race-is-a-construct-why-should-we-even-acknowledge-racism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-see-color-by-seeing-racism-in-all-things-youre-perpetuating-it-if-race-is-a-construct-why-should-we-even-acknowledge-racism/</guid>
      <description>Recognizing race as a social construct does not make race less &amp;ldquo;real.&amp;rdquo;
Money is a social construct, but you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t burn your wallet, right?
Scientists generally do not recognize &amp;ldquo;race&amp;rdquo; as biologically meaningful, but race is socially real, not biologically real.
Race as a social construct is contingent on social groups and their collective agreement and acceptance of the constructions.
Race is something that is real in society, and that shapes the way we see ourselves and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve never personally done anything to oppress Black people (or any oppressed group).</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/ive-never-personally-done-anything-to-oppress-black-people-or-any-oppressed-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/ive-never-personally-done-anything-to-oppress-black-people-or-any-oppressed-group/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s good to hear. Now let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the institutions that oppress Black people and other people of color.
Structural racism is pervasive in U.S. policies, organizations, and across institutional domains, producing and sustaining racial inequality.
In the educational system, for example, minority students are graded differently and are disproportionately disciplined, and this causes many Black students to get left behind in said system, while their white counterparts move ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why separate yourselves from everyone else? Isn&#39;t that racist?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-separate-yourselves-from-everyone-else-isnt-that-racist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-separate-yourselves-from-everyone-else-isnt-that-racist/</guid>
      <description>We can not just advocate for ending Capitalist oppression, but we can also put specific ways in which the Black community is oppressed in the spotlight, while advocating for equality.
Not having that additional input from a marginalized community might end up perpetuating oppression from society, even if the socialist revolution succeeds.
This might be independent from actual policy. Maybe a Socialist leader is not antisemitic or racist, but without educating the people, any socialist policy&amp;rsquo;s effect will be dampened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You call everyone you don&#39;t like a racist/fascist.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/you-call-everyone-you-dont-like-a-racistfascist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/you-call-everyone-you-dont-like-a-racistfascist/</guid>
      <description>Technically, it is correct that anyone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t defend marginalized people who look physically different than them, even when choosing to be neutral, is a racist in some way.
The foundation of Western society is based upon the construction of whiteness, which led to white supremacy. Those who are not being oppressed by the system of whiteness are usually those who uphold this system, and deny that systemic racism exists. These people who consciously or unconsciously defend whiteness could be anyone from average working-class folks, to Liberals, to &amp;ldquo;Brocialists,&amp;rdquo; to all-out reactionaries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>