<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>race on Leftpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/race/</link>
    <description>Recent content in race on Leftpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/race/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t see color. By seeing racism in all things, you&#39;re perpetuating it. If race is a construct why should we even acknowledge racism?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-see-color-by-seeing-racism-in-all-things-youre-perpetuating-it-if-race-is-a-construct-why-should-we-even-acknowledge-racism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-see-color-by-seeing-racism-in-all-things-youre-perpetuating-it-if-race-is-a-construct-why-should-we-even-acknowledge-racism/</guid>
      <description>Recognizing race as a social construct does not make race less &amp;ldquo;real.&amp;rdquo;
Money is a social construct, but you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t burn your wallet, right?
Scientists generally do not recognize &amp;ldquo;race&amp;rdquo; as biologically meaningful, but race is socially real, not biologically real.
Race as a social construct is contingent on social groups and their collective agreement and acceptance of the constructions.
Race is something that is real in society, and that shapes the way we see ourselves and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not EVERYTHING is about race. And isn&#39;t pointing out race just being racist, encouraging racism, or dividing us further?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/not-everything-is-about-race-and-isnt-pointing-out-race-just-being-racist-encouraging-racism-or-dividing-us-further/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/not-everything-is-about-race-and-isnt-pointing-out-race-just-being-racist-encouraging-racism-or-dividing-us-further/</guid>
      <description>In an ideal, post-racial world, yes.
But we do not live in this ideal, post-racial world.
We must address the very real, systemic racism together in order to work through the divisions and bring everyone onto the same page of action.
Furthermore, it is worth keeping in mind that Black Americans are not responsible for &amp;ldquo;race.&amp;rdquo; It is &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; people (Europeans) who created and developed &amp;ldquo;race&amp;rdquo; as a social construct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why does everything always have to be about race? Why do people always have to bring race into it?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-does-everything-always-have-to-be-about-race-why-do-people-always-have-to-bring-race-into-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-does-everything-always-have-to-be-about-race-why-do-people-always-have-to-bring-race-into-it/</guid>
      <description>Because the color of your skin predicts many of the outcomes you will experience in your life.
Where racists will point to these facts and, incorrectly, claim these are essential and immutable qualities of the races, Socialists understand that these material conditions are caused by institutions of power, both formal and informal, that exist to support some over others (principally, the ruling class over the working class).
Because race can be used as a wedge to divide us, society is structured to benefit some people over others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>