<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Political Correctness on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/political-correctness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Political Correctness on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/political-correctness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I agree with what you&#39;re saying, just not with how you&#39;re saying it.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-agree-with-what-youre-saying-just-not-with-how-youre-saying-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-agree-with-what-youre-saying-just-not-with-how-youre-saying-it/</guid>
      <description>This is called tone policing.
This implies that rhetoric matters more to you than actual ideas.
There is a time for a discussion of optics, but this is not usually appropriate over matters dealing with race and/or class.
One should judge ideas based off of what they are, not by how they are presented, although presentation and clarity play a significant role in our communications.
Obviously saying &amp;ldquo;white people are racist&amp;rdquo; (for example) is so simplistic that it&amp;rsquo;s almost useless, but if one knows how to read these statements and the intent behind them, then there is no problem in most cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racism isn&#39;t prominent; the Liberal media just blows it up so it seems that way to push their anti-cop agenda.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/racism-isnt-prominent-the-liberal-media-just-blows-it-up-so-it-seems-that-way-to-push-their-anti-cop-agenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/racism-isnt-prominent-the-liberal-media-just-blows-it-up-so-it-seems-that-way-to-push-their-anti-cop-agenda/</guid>
      <description>You already know what we&amp;rsquo;re gonna say about the racism thing (come on, we all have social media and smartphones, so if you want to see racism in action today, just head on over to YouTube or Twitter and do a simple search), but let&amp;rsquo;s address the Liberal media thing, because we don&amp;rsquo;t really like Liberal or Conservative media very much (and that&amp;rsquo;s putting it lightly).
The relationships between institutions such as the mainstream media and police must be understood in the larger context of Capitalism as a class-based economic system that benefits from and contributes to racism and violence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The reason racism is a problem is because people keep looking for ways to be offended</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-reason-racism-is-a-problem-is-because-people-keep-looking-for-ways-to-be-offended/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-reason-racism-is-a-problem-is-because-people-keep-looking-for-ways-to-be-offended/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ways to be offended&amp;rdquo; is a common phrase among Conservatives reacting to &amp;ldquo;Political Correctness.&amp;rdquo; It is an example of how mainstream media exploits public fear and hatred as a social control mechanism.
There are various theories about the origins of the actual phrase, but until the 1980s in the United States, it was usually used ironically exclusively by the Left. It didn&amp;rsquo;t surface in mainstream American culture until 1990 when Richard Bernstein used it in a New York Times article to describe &amp;ldquo;unofficial ideology of the university .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugh, do you always have to be so politically correct?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/ugh-do-you-always-have-to-be-so-politically-correct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/ugh-do-you-always-have-to-be-so-politically-correct/</guid>
      <description>Is the &amp;ldquo;politically correct&amp;rdquo; take something that you agree with deep down, but are too lazy to actually reflect in your own actions and/or words?
We understand that we are all conditioned and therefore carrying with us negative ideas or perspectives rooted in our childhoods or traditions, but it is on all of us to actively work to be better people.
Having some room to breathe and not overthink things is important, but if your words are reflecting negative ideas or sentiments, even though your intentions might not be in a bad place, it might be worth it to pause and reflect on what it is that you are promoting, and asking yourself if this is something that is in line with who you want to be as a human being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happened to free speech? I can&#39;t say anything anymore without someone taking offense. PC culture is out of control!</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/what-happened-to-free-speech-i-cant-say-anything-anymore-without-someone-taking-offense-pc-culture-is-out-of-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/what-happened-to-free-speech-i-cant-say-anything-anymore-without-someone-taking-offense-pc-culture-is-out-of-control/</guid>
      <description>What happened to free speech in the context of &amp;ldquo;PC culture&amp;rdquo; is, at its core, dishonest.
The &amp;ldquo;free speech&amp;rdquo; argument displays a political spin of the group that has its hands on it.
It is used as a political tool rather than a concept to keep the combatants in the political arena honest.
There are no official rules, guidelines, or laws in favor of political correctness and against offensive speech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>