<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Immigration on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/immigration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Immigration on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/immigration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want to live in America speak English.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/if-you-want-to-live-in-america-speak-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/if-you-want-to-live-in-america-speak-english/</guid>
      <description>If your ancestors wanted to live in America, maybe they should have learned some Indigenous/Native American languages (as well as some other things).
Okay, in all seriousness&amp;hellip;
The demand for immigrants to speak English is an ethnocentric mandate for cultural assimilation into a system of multicultural intolerance (translation: this is a self-centered, selfish, and narcissistic demand to make, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t sit on fair, even grounds).
The idea that penniless immigrants once came to this country and worked low-paying jobs to pull themselves up by their bootstraps to eventually reach equality of skills and income with &amp;ldquo;natives&amp;rdquo; is mostly false.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The immigrants are coming in and taking our jobs. They&#39;re also bringing crime.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-immigrants-are-coming-in-and-taking-our-jobs-theyre-also-bringing-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-immigrants-are-coming-in-and-taking-our-jobs-theyre-also-bringing-crime/</guid>
      <description>Immigrants largely work jobs that Americans no longer want to work, largely in the agriculture sector. Immigrants (undocumented and documented) also pay into the tax system in a net gain for the U.S. treasury. Additionally, U.S. birthrates are low to the point we need immigrants to help fill the gap (see here and here).
States with high levels of immigrants also see a LOWERING in crime rates. Immigrants (both documented and undocumented) commit fewer crimes than native born residents (see here and here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Those refugees should fight for their own countries rather than flee and come here. They&#39;re cowards and just want job opportunities.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/those-refugees-should-fight-for-their-own-countries-rather-than-flee-and-come-here-theyre-cowards-and-just-want-job-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/those-refugees-should-fight-for-their-own-countries-rather-than-flee-and-come-here-theyre-cowards-and-just-want-job-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Most of the refugees you&amp;rsquo;re referencing are probably refugees because of American foreign policy.
Telling people displaced and suffering because of policies put in place by your government to &amp;ldquo;stay and fight&amp;rdquo; is not only deeply inhumane, but nonsensical.
Also, who are these refugees supposed to fight for?
In a civil war, there are no obvious invading and defending forces.
 Source: https://blacksocialists.us/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>