<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reverse racism on Leftpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/reverse-racism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reverse racism on Leftpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/reverse-racism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Black people can be racist too; it&#39;s not just white people.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/black-people-can-be-racist-too-its-not-just-white-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/black-people-can-be-racist-too-its-not-just-white-people/</guid>
      <description>This all depends on what you mean when you say &amp;ldquo;racist.&amp;rdquo; Usually when someone says this, what they&amp;rsquo;re really trying to do is equate prejudices expressed or acted upon by Black Americans with the racism and prejudice of &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; Americans. This leaves out centuries of historical context, as well as the context of our present circumstances. Black Americans only make up 12.6% of the U.S. population and &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; Americans hold most of the institutional power, so it&amp;rsquo;s worth thinking about the big picture here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not EVERYTHING is about race. And isn&#39;t pointing out race just being racist, encouraging racism, or dividing us further?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/not-everything-is-about-race-and-isnt-pointing-out-race-just-being-racist-encouraging-racism-or-dividing-us-further/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/not-everything-is-about-race-and-isnt-pointing-out-race-just-being-racist-encouraging-racism-or-dividing-us-further/</guid>
      <description>In an ideal, post-racial world, yes.
But we do not live in this ideal, post-racial world.
We must address the very real, systemic racism together in order to work through the divisions and bring everyone onto the same page of action.
Furthermore, it is worth keeping in mind that Black Americans are not responsible for &amp;ldquo;race.&amp;rdquo; It is &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; people (Europeans) who created and developed &amp;ldquo;race&amp;rdquo; as a social construct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why separate yourselves from everyone else? Isn&#39;t that racist?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-separate-yourselves-from-everyone-else-isnt-that-racist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-separate-yourselves-from-everyone-else-isnt-that-racist/</guid>
      <description>We can not just advocate for ending Capitalist oppression, but we can also put specific ways in which the Black community is oppressed in the spotlight, while advocating for equality.
Not having that additional input from a marginalized community might end up perpetuating oppression from society, even if the socialist revolution succeeds.
This might be independent from actual policy. Maybe a Socialist leader is not antisemitic or racist, but without educating the people, any socialist policy&amp;rsquo;s effect will be dampened.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>