<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>racism on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/racism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in racism on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/racism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t see color. By seeing racism in all things, you&#39;re perpetuating it. If race is a construct why should we even acknowledge racism?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-see-color-by-seeing-racism-in-all-things-youre-perpetuating-it-if-race-is-a-construct-why-should-we-even-acknowledge-racism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-see-color-by-seeing-racism-in-all-things-youre-perpetuating-it-if-race-is-a-construct-why-should-we-even-acknowledge-racism/</guid>
      <description>Recognizing race as a social construct does not make race less &amp;ldquo;real.&amp;rdquo;
Money is a social construct, but you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t burn your wallet, right?
Scientists generally do not recognize &amp;ldquo;race&amp;rdquo; as biologically meaningful, but race is socially real, not biologically real.
Race as a social construct is contingent on social groups and their collective agreement and acceptance of the constructions.
Race is something that is real in society, and that shapes the way we see ourselves and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My [insert POC] friend&#39;s family is doing better than me, so how can racism exist?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/my-insert-poc-friends-family-is-doing-better-than-me-so-how-can-racism-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/my-insert-poc-friends-family-is-doing-better-than-me-so-how-can-racism-exist/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s simply anecdotal. If all [POC] were like your friend, we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be having this discussion in the first place.
 Source: https://blacksocialists.us/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not EVERYTHING is about race. And isn&#39;t pointing out race just being racist, encouraging racism, or dividing us further?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/not-everything-is-about-race-and-isnt-pointing-out-race-just-being-racist-encouraging-racism-or-dividing-us-further/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/not-everything-is-about-race-and-isnt-pointing-out-race-just-being-racist-encouraging-racism-or-dividing-us-further/</guid>
      <description>In an ideal, post-racial world, yes.
But we do not live in this ideal, post-racial world.
We must address the very real, systemic racism together in order to work through the divisions and bring everyone onto the same page of action.
Furthermore, it is worth keeping in mind that Black Americans are not responsible for &amp;ldquo;race.&amp;rdquo; It is &amp;ldquo;white&amp;rdquo; people (Europeans) who created and developed &amp;ldquo;race&amp;rdquo; as a social construct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racism is just a thing that exists, like potholes. You have to understand that you can&#39;t get rid of it. It&#39;s natural to fear the other, and people organize along racial lines for this reason.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/racism-is-just-a-thing-that-exists-like-potholes-you-have-to-understand-that-you-cant-get-rid-of-it-its-natural-to-fear-the-other-and-people-organize-along-racial-lines-for-this-reason/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/racism-is-just-a-thing-that-exists-like-potholes-you-have-to-understand-that-you-cant-get-rid-of-it-its-natural-to-fear-the-other-and-people-organize-along-racial-lines-for-this-reason/</guid>
      <description>Do you recommend we just live with potholes, or should we fix them?
Who defines the &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; and how do they define it? And why is it considered &amp;ldquo;natural&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;fear&amp;rdquo; those who are different? Perhaps the solution is making it so that there is no fear between different people, and bringing people together both socially and economically.
People organize around &amp;ldquo;racial&amp;rdquo; lines in America because of the racialized institutions in our society, as well as their colonialist, white supremacist roots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racism isn&#39;t prominent; the Liberal media just blows it up so it seems that way to push their anti-cop agenda.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/racism-isnt-prominent-the-liberal-media-just-blows-it-up-so-it-seems-that-way-to-push-their-anti-cop-agenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/racism-isnt-prominent-the-liberal-media-just-blows-it-up-so-it-seems-that-way-to-push-their-anti-cop-agenda/</guid>
      <description>You already know what we&amp;rsquo;re gonna say about the racism thing (come on, we all have social media and smartphones, so if you want to see racism in action today, just head on over to YouTube or Twitter and do a simple search), but let&amp;rsquo;s address the Liberal media thing, because we don&amp;rsquo;t really like Liberal or Conservative media very much (and that&amp;rsquo;s putting it lightly).
The relationships between institutions such as the mainstream media and police must be understood in the larger context of Capitalism as a class-based economic system that benefits from and contributes to racism and violence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The reason racism is a problem is because people keep looking for ways to be offended</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-reason-racism-is-a-problem-is-because-people-keep-looking-for-ways-to-be-offended/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-reason-racism-is-a-problem-is-because-people-keep-looking-for-ways-to-be-offended/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ways to be offended&amp;rdquo; is a common phrase among Conservatives reacting to &amp;ldquo;Political Correctness.&amp;rdquo; It is an example of how mainstream media exploits public fear and hatred as a social control mechanism.
There are various theories about the origins of the actual phrase, but until the 1980s in the United States, it was usually used ironically exclusively by the Left. It didn&amp;rsquo;t surface in mainstream American culture until 1990 when Richard Bernstein used it in a New York Times article to describe &amp;ldquo;unofficial ideology of the university .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You call everyone you don&#39;t like a racist/fascist.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/you-call-everyone-you-dont-like-a-racistfascist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/you-call-everyone-you-dont-like-a-racistfascist/</guid>
      <description>Technically, it is correct that anyone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t defend marginalized people who look physically different than them, even when choosing to be neutral, is a racist in some way.
The foundation of Western society is based upon the construction of whiteness, which led to white supremacy. Those who are not being oppressed by the system of whiteness are usually those who uphold this system, and deny that systemic racism exists. These people who consciously or unconsciously defend whiteness could be anyone from average working-class folks, to Liberals, to &amp;ldquo;Brocialists,&amp;rdquo; to all-out reactionaries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>