<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fathers on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/fathers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fathers on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/fathers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The problem is too many Black single parents.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-problem-is-too-many-black-single-parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/the-problem-is-too-many-black-single-parents/</guid>
      <description>Although the prevalence of single parenthood is definitely an issue, it is not thee problem.
Thee problem is and always has been colonialism, capitalism, imperialism, and white supremacy (amongst many other things).
We have to ask ourselves why this particular issue that is mentioned is indeed so common, and analyze the issue through a more structuralist framework.
Black Americans are more negatively impacted by our racist criminal justice system and are therefore more likely to go to jail than if they were white.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why don&#39;t we talk about Black fatherlessness and what that does, or gun violence in Black communities?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-dont-we-talk-about-black-fatherlessness-and-what-that-does-or-gun-violence-in-black-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/why-dont-we-talk-about-black-fatherlessness-and-what-that-does-or-gun-violence-in-black-communities/</guid>
      <description>Black fatherlessness and gun violence are things that are absolutely talked about within America, but the biggest problem here is with regard to the diagnosis of why these issues are so prevalent and what the solutions are to fix them.
The attack on the &amp;ldquo;Black family&amp;rdquo; and the scourge of gun violence can be traced to some clear material causes:
  The drug wars that disproportionately target Black communities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>