<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Selfishness on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/selfishness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Selfishness on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/selfishness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>At what level does it become about personal responsibility?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/at-what-level-does-it-become-about-personal-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/at-what-level-does-it-become-about-personal-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>Eugene Debs wasn&amp;rsquo;t right about everything, but he was certainly right about a lot.
We&amp;rsquo;ll leave you with this quote from him that is a core part of our philosophy:
&amp;ldquo;While there is a lower class, I am in it.
While there is a criminal element, I am of it.
And while there is a soul in prison, I am not free.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does it actually really affect you though? Why care so much if it doesn&#39;t affect you?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/does-it-actually-really-affect-you-though-why-care-so-much-if-it-doesnt-affect-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/does-it-actually-really-affect-you-though-why-care-so-much-if-it-doesnt-affect-you/</guid>
      <description>Many of our white comrades would say that our struggles do affect them, and that even if they didn&amp;rsquo;t, they would still care because they have a base level of care for other human beings.
Other people matter.
But let&amp;rsquo;s go one step further and say that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t affect you and other people don&amp;rsquo;t matter. It may very well affect you in the future, may it not? Why let it get to that point?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I care more about me and my family&#39;s wellbeing</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-care-more-about-me-and-my-familys-wellbeing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-care-more-about-me-and-my-familys-wellbeing/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d be had pressed to find someone who cared more about strangers than they cared about themselves and their immediate relatives and friends. Socialism can however be promoted based on purely selfish reasons if you so choose. If your friends or your family get sick or lose their jobs, do you want to be the one who has to take care of them and bear that financial burden? Probably not - so why not support a free and universal healthcare system, or a better unemployment system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I don&#39;t want my money/taxes subsidizing those lazy welfare folk. I certainly worked hard, so why can&#39;t the poor?</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-want-my-moneytaxes-subsidizing-those-lazy-welfare-folk-i-certainly-worked-hard-so-why-cant-the-poor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/i-dont-want-my-moneytaxes-subsidizing-those-lazy-welfare-folk-i-certainly-worked-hard-so-why-cant-the-poor/</guid>
      <description>Most states require those on welfare to have a job or be job-searching, and the most effective welfare programs are those which give money to low-income workers.
The poor work harder than the average millionaire, taking sometimes two jobs just trying to avoid starvation and homelessness, and if they DO reach homelessness, no company will hire them since they will have no fixed address.
On the other hand, you have people who were born into wealthy families and haven&amp;rsquo;t worked hard for much of anything, or at best had a radically easier start than most others within society.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>