<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>class on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/class/</link>
    <description>Recent content in class on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/tags/class/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity politics make everything about race. This is really about class.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/identity-politics-make-everything-about-race-this-is-really-about-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/identity-politics-make-everything-about-race-this-is-really-about-class/</guid>
      <description>Identity politics is not synonymous with race reductionism (reducing everything to race).
We think it&amp;rsquo;s important that we differentiate between Liberal identity politics, and Leftist identity politics. The former is a tool used by (Neo)Liberals to keep poor and working-class people divided, while the latter is about ensuring less-represented voices and concerns get heard in an international movement to dismantle Capitalism.
If anything, class reductionism has &amp;ldquo;ruined&amp;rdquo; the (actual) Left while Liberals (not Leftists) with no conception of an anti-racist and anti-capitalist future have co-opted inherently anticapitalist concepts rooted in identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If we focus on class only, the racial problems will fix themselves.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/if-we-focus-on-class-only-the-racial-problems-will-fix-themselves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/if-we-focus-on-class-only-the-racial-problems-will-fix-themselves/</guid>
      <description>This ignores some&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s say &amp;ldquo;questionable&amp;rdquo; policies by certain &amp;ldquo;socialist&amp;rdquo; governments in the past, like the relocation of the Tatars in the USSR, for example.
It also ignores Third Positionism as a potential &amp;ldquo;socialist&amp;rdquo; position that addresses one thing, but not the other.
So while nationalism and race can be understood as a construct used by the bourgeoisie to divide and control the proletariat, it historically has not been that simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leftism is just for comfortable white BernieBros who want a political club. Focusing on class automatically ignores race and gender.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/leftism-is-just-for-comfortable-white-berniebros-who-want-a-political-club-focusing-on-class-automatically-ignores-race-and-gender/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/leftism-is-just-for-comfortable-white-berniebros-who-want-a-political-club-focusing-on-class-automatically-ignores-race-and-gender/</guid>
      <description>Did systemic racism as we understand it today exist prior to Capitalism (mercantile or otherwise)?
Racial categories were originally created to define an economic class: slaves.
In addition, they served as an ideological tool to prevent poor whites from allying with Black people who actually share their class interests.
Gender has also been used in order to regulate social roles.
These aren&amp;rsquo;t separate systems of oppression that &amp;ldquo;occasionally&amp;rdquo; intersect; they are fundamentally interconnected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need to focus on class instead of race.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/we-need-to-focus-on-class-instead-of-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/we-need-to-focus-on-class-instead-of-race/</guid>
      <description>This is a false dichotomy.
We can and must focus on both class and race, for they are interconnected and play off of one another.
 Source: https://blacksocialists.us/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>