<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pessimism on Workerpedia</title>
    <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/pessimism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pessimism on Workerpedia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/categories/pessimism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Communism sounds good in theory, but it doesn&#39;t work in practice. Just look at countries like Venezuela. Look at what happened in Russia (the USSR).</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/communism-sounds-good-in-theory-but-it-doesnt-work-in-practice-just-look-at-countries-like-venezuela-look-at-what-happened-in-russia-the-ussr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/communism-sounds-good-in-theory-but-it-doesnt-work-in-practice-just-look-at-countries-like-venezuela-look-at-what-happened-in-russia-the-ussr/</guid>
      <description>It is important to differentiate between a socialist/communist society, and a &amp;ldquo;socialist/communist&amp;rdquo; state (the latter does not exist beyond a mere label, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean much).
Venezuela is not a socialist country. It has State Capitalism and used oil money to fund welfare programs when oil production was high and prices were solid.
It&amp;rsquo;s also heavily sanctioned by foreign nations such as the United States.
The USSR also represented State Capitalism and faced several challenges, including a massive drought, and was actively worked against by foreign nations such as the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m a realist. What you&#39;re doing is utopian.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/im-a-realist-what-youre-doing-is-utopian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/im-a-realist-what-youre-doing-is-utopian/</guid>
      <description>We strongly disagree, but if what we are aiming to accomplish is merely &amp;ldquo;utopian&amp;rdquo; in your eyes (it&amp;rsquo;s not in ours), that means you can at least see the good in it.
You have one life; maybe help us create a new, &amp;ldquo;realistic&amp;rdquo; version of what we are aiming towards.
If the problem is that it&amp;rsquo;s not realistic, then join the discussion and help ground us. None of us here are dedicated to having our heads up our asses; we just want a better world than the one we are in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian influence over our elections is a bigger concern/threat than American racial grievances.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/russian-influence-over-our-elections-is-a-bigger-concernthreat-than-american-racial-grievances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/russian-influence-over-our-elections-is-a-bigger-concernthreat-than-american-racial-grievances/</guid>
      <description>What a, dare we say&amp;hellip; privileged position to take.
This stance completely overlooks the reality of voter suppression that Black Americans and other ethnic minorities have had to deal with.
Gerrymandering, social media manipulation, ex-offenders being indefinitely stripped of voting rights, and all forms of voter suppression are a far bigger threat to our semi-democratic institutions (what many call &amp;ldquo;democracy,&amp;rdquo; although we understand that Liberal representative &amp;ldquo;democracy&amp;rdquo; isn&amp;rsquo;t democracy at all) than Russian influence over our elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop making excuses and get over the past.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/stop-making-excuses-and-get-over-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/stop-making-excuses-and-get-over-the-past/</guid>
      <description>We slash your car tires.
You say, &amp;ldquo;Why&amp;rsquo;d you do that? Now I can&amp;rsquo;t drive.&amp;quot;
We say, &amp;ldquo;Do what? Stop making excuses and get over the past.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True equality is impossible</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/true-equality-is-impossible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/true-equality-is-impossible/</guid>
      <description>Equality is not &amp;ldquo;sameness.&amp;rdquo;
Equality acknowledges differences between people, but does not support distinctions such as race and gender as a basis for subjection.
Acknowledging differences is at the core of the concept of equality. In order for us to treat each other as equals, it is necessary that we first acknowledge and value our differences.
Treating people as equals is different than treating them the same. For instance, in education, giving students the same amounts of instruction, lessons, and identical learning materials is different than providing students with the necessary resources to reach educational goals and achieve academic success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re just going to stir up trouble and make things worse for everyone with this Socialism crap.</title>
      <link>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/youre-just-going-to-stir-up-trouble-and-make-things-worse-for-everyone-with-this-socialism-crap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://idc-snoe.github.io/idc-answers/claims/youre-just-going-to-stir-up-trouble-and-make-things-worse-for-everyone-with-this-socialism-crap/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;trouble&amp;rdquo; is already here and more &amp;ldquo;trouble&amp;rdquo; is coming.
People are starving or working double jobs without resting to just barely not starve.
People are being killed because of their skin color, sex, gender, or age.
People have to work in shit they never really wanted to do because otherwise they&amp;rsquo;ll be left in worse conditions than a family goldfish.
The only people to have &amp;ldquo;things made worse&amp;rdquo; for are the rich, privileged few, which are in their position thanks to how bad life is for the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>